https://www.john-skinner.co.uk/terms-privacy/

Terms & Conditions of Sale
Please view the PDF for our full terms and conditions – JSM – Terms & Conditions of Sale
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how John Skinner (Manufacturing) Ltd uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.
John Skinner (Manufacturing) Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
John Skinner (Manufacturing) Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from July 2013.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information. If you do not wish us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may write to or email us.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Show Panel
Coronavirus Update (November 2020)
We continue to remain open and functional.
We have implemented many changes to our factory unit, and our staff are working staggered hours to allow for better social distancing. Some staff, however, still cannot return to work due to vulnerable situations and childcare/school issues.
We are doing our best to manage and cope – and we continue to appreciate your patience during this time.  Whilst your life may have returned to normal, this, unfortunately, is not the case for all of us, so please keep this in mind. Remember, our number one priority is the health and safety of our staff.
Enquiries
At this present time, we would prefer enquiries via email/contact form as this allows Jonathon Skinner to focus his efforts on the production floor.
However, we are happy to arrange a call back to discuss the finer points of your enquiry, so please do let us know.
Production/Lead Times/Shipping
Production of parts and shipping is on-going.
Due to the aforementioned issues, production time/lead times continue to be affected.
Plan Wisely for the Future
In our view, 2020 should essentially be written-off as most car shows and events have been or will be cancelled. Instead of panicking, rushing and getting frustrated about the situation – use the remaining months of the year wisely. Take your time and restore your car to the level it deserves using a Skinner Kit. When the season arrives in 2021, you will benefit from your hard work and patience undertaken during this testing year.
Thank you all, once again, for your continued support and most of all your patience during these strange times.
Stay healthy,
The John Skinner Team
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
